This is a trap.
It was snapped intentionally.
You knew we wouldn't fail to notice it,
so marching into the forest must
be exactly what you want us to do.
I've seen through your ploy!
Why don't you give it up and come on out?
The Fly Swordsman, a subordinate
who appears in the legend
of the Lord of the Flies, hmm?
I don't know who you are,
but if you hand over the leopardman
and the girl, I'll spare your life.
Better yet, I'll even welcome
you into the ranks of Ashint.
You seem to be a rather skilled warrior.
And if I refuse?
Then I'll bestow suffering with my curses.
Suffering so great you'll rue being alive.
Even the Five Dragoons could
not fend off our curses.
You claim to be the ones who slew them?
Yes. Even Humanity's Strongest
was powerless before our curses.
Promise me you'll guarantee
Eve and that girl's safety.
You have my word on the matter.
Very well. Then I'll lead you to them.
Everyone, please follow me.
I see.
Halt, all of you.
You have no intention
of simply handing them over.
Isn't that right?
DARK PLOT ~MISSING~
- How...?
- You wording gave you away.
DARK PLOT ~MISSING~
- Just now, you said "everyone."
Just now, you said "everyone."
A few men would be plenty
to accompany you.
But you were trying to lead us
all into the woods.
Perhaps you need us in
range for something. Is that it?
Maintain your distance
and prepare to attack, men.
I thought you were going to kill me
with your masterful curses.
I'll let you in on a little secret.
My Ashint soldiers here are
the successors of the assassin's guild.
A hero from another world once declared
the guild evil and exterminated it,
but we've taken up their line of work
as users of curse magic.
So you use poisons?
Correct.
Incredibly advanced ones.
Ones that can only be synthesized via
special techniques passed down
among the few survivors
of the assassin's guild.
So they kill people with advanced
poison that leaves no trace.
That's the true nature of their "curses."
Then the tragedy of the Black
Dragon Knights fell into our lap.
The sudden demise of the Five Dragoons
heralded as the strongest alive—
Could only be explained by curses
beyond human understanding.
You are wonderfully quick on the uptake.
That is why we proclaimed ourselves
the slayers of the Five Dragoons.
We decided it was the perfect opportunity
to foster belief in our curses.
No one can prove they aren't real!
Maybe it really was a curse!
So long as such uncertainty remains,
we come out on top no matter what!
In this world, without any proof,
those with the loudest claim take all!
So what is your ultimate goal?
We're going to use Duke Zuan to carve out
a central role for us in this nation.
All while assassinating
those who get in your way?
Yes!
In the end, we'll take
the country for ourselves.
By the way, where are your other allies?
Aside from Eve and the girl, it's just me.
I find it hard to believe you planned
to face us all by yourself.
Then allow me to explain.
You see, I'm the one who survived
facing down the Five Dragoons.
To think the Fly Swordsman is
actually the famous Seras Ashrain...
Though it's all starting to come together.
So, you slew the Five Dragoons?
And if I did?
No, it couldn't have been you.
Why do you think that?
It's simple.
I don't believe you could best
Humanity's Strongest.
This is the man set to be that
leopardman's final bloodsport opponent.
His name's Belgar.
And this over here
is Belgar's older brother, Varragan.
These two are Ashint's strongest siblings.
And what an odd twist of fate,
for they had a younger brother named Zarash.
That's right.
They're the older brothers of the Fang,
who was pursuing you.
Now what will you do,
Seras Ashrain?
My subordinates have already
circled around behind you.
Shocked, are you?
Indeed, we were just a decoy.
Cloaking one's presence
and sneaking up on a target
is an art all assassins master.
That said...
You have a terribly
pretty face, don't you?
I think I'll need to take my time
granting you my personal blessing
and reforming you as a proper
devotee of the curse god.
No matter how strong you may be,
all are powerless before the status
ailment caused by our curse!
This is the end for you.
Now, bend a knee where you stand.
Seras Ashrain,
I shall grant you the honor
of one day bearing my child.
Sir Tooka...
It's your...
OFFENSIVE FORM:
FINAL ACCELERATION
- Assault Accel.
Let me demonstrate a "curse"
you're unfamiliar with.
Paralyze!
Guess you didn't think I'd have
an attack with this kind of range.
Wh-Where's our detachment?
I already crushed them.
All fifteen men while
you were blabbing away.
Poison.
You were keen enough to notice
that Eve was up to something,
so I knew you'd catch
that intentionally broken branch
and avoid entering the forest
for fear of a trap.
Which is why...
Act like you're trying to lure
them all into the forest.
I tipped you off that something was afoot
and had you suss it out yourself
to make you feel in control,
confident that your judgment was sound.
Yet that's exactly what
paralyzed your analysis,
acting like a poison.
It went exactly as you predicted, my liege.
You played along with him
to buy time for us.
His mistake was not considering
the possibility of a greater ploy.
Seras, I was right to leave him to you.
I'm glad I was able to help.
Could you go back and update
Eve on the situation?
Yes. Consider it done.
They've turned back, huh?
My real trap would be incomplete
if the first wave didn't return.
Piggymaru, let's connect again.
What's the matter?
Sorry.
I didn't even think about
the toll on you. My bad.
So not even you can predict everything, huh?
Allow me to aid you.
All right. Seras, take care of Lis.
Yes. I'm counting on you, Eve.
Yes.
Big Sis, don't worry about me.
She'll be safe with Seras.
Have no fear.
Can you get an accurate
headcount on the first wave?
Got it.
We've finally found you, Eve Speed!
We'll drag your pathetic leopardman
corpse before the duke!
Your head is mine!
Paralyze!
Poison!
Tooka.
Yeah, I know.
There's nowhere left for you to run,
you ungrateful mockery of a human!
You can run, but it's futile, futile, futile!
Duke Zuan...
Rejoice, Eve Speed.
The duke will mount your head on a pike
and have that girl wear garb
made from your pelt.
You'll be together forever,
happily ever after.
And once I sell her off to a brothel,
I'll make her wear a leopard mask
while she serves her customers!
You're definitely scum.
Paralyze.
You have maxed out active targets.
INFLICT PARALYSIS, PARALYZE
MAXIMUM TARGETS
- There's a target cap?
Dark.
What?! My vision is going!
Dark!
My eyes!
Eve!
Kill anyone who turns to flee!
Let no one escape!
Understood!
UNIQUE SKILL: INFLICT STATUS AILMENT/USABLE
INFLICT PARALYSIS, PARALYZE: LV 3
MAXIMUM TARGETS: 76/80
- Die, die, die!
- Dark.
S-Spare me!
I won't allow any of you to run!
Hurry up and kill that creepy man in the robe!
You hear me?! I'm your duke!
I will have my way with everything here!
Now kill him already!
Damn it, damn it, damn it!
- You bastards!
- Looks like I don't even need
Berserk to drive the duke mad.
Looks like I don't even need
Tooka, I must thank you.
Even though I'm a warrior,
I was beginning to think I'd
had enough of battle.
But I feel delight once more
as I fight alongside you like this.
Spare me!
S-Stay back!
I'll remember this!
And I shall not let it stand!
In the near future, I'll see
that you meet a cruel end!
Paralyze.
Are you stupid?
Did you really think
we'd just acquiesce and let you go?
Be done with him.
If you had only sought to play me,
I might have forgiven you.
But...
But instead, you tried
to go after the girl too!
Farewell.
Looks like it's over.
Seras, could you take Lis
and prepare to depart?
Certainly.
Thanks.
Also, thank you for the backup with a bow.
I'm sorry I acted without orders.
You're already the vice captain
of this mercenary group.
When I'm not able to make the calls,
I leave that to you.
You're good with that, right, Eve? Lis?
- Indeed.
- Yes.
Good. We didn't let anyone escape.
Freeze.
When inflicted on a living target, it
encases them in ridiculously strong ice.
But this unique skill treats corpses as
objects, which can be crushed into powder.
What are you attempting to do?
With this skill, I can get rid
of the bodies without a trace.
These curse magic users
claim to have slain the Five Dragoons.
So I figure I can pin that
on them forever now.
No one can prove that curses aren't real.
Oh, how proudly you boasted about that.
Now no one will ever be able
to prove you were real either!
Ashint has vanished?!
All that remained at the scene were the
corpses of the duke and his private army.
Now my plan to use them
as pawns is ruined....
Moreover, how will I
explain this to the goddess?
If this sours her mood, then...
Find them!
Do everything you can to find Ashint!
Understood?!
What's the matter?
W-Well...
I wonder if I'll grow like you have.
Wh-What do you mean?
The proprietress said that
if my breasts didn't grow,
then I wouldn't be treated as
a proper woman in the future.
- then I wouldn't be treated as
- That's not true.
Everything that woman forced
upon you was wrong.
So please forget everything she said.
Forget everything...?
Yes.
From now on, you should only let the words
of those you trust take root in your heart.
Then I'd like to let your
words take root, Miss Seras.
In that case, I'll do my best
to make more time to chat.
It's like I have another big sister now.
I'll take watch, so please get some rest.
No, my eyes are wide awake.
I doubt I could sleep.
Shall I lend you this?
You might slumber peacefully resting here.
You're just as tired too, aren't you?
If you'd like,
I could lend you mine.
Um, did you... mean that as a joke?
Pardon me.
Stuff like this isn't so bad now and again.
I-I'm grateful for your courtesy.
To be honest, I've been
curious for a while now.
Would you mind...
if I touched your elven ears?
Go right ahead if you'd like.
Then...
What do you think?
It's kind of a strange sensation.
S-Sir Tooka, that...!
Ah, sorry.
I-It's fine.
This might be rude to ask,
but do you have any special
feelings toward Eve or Lis?
Why would you think so?
The way you interact with them feels gentle.
Like it does with me.
Well, I guess it's for the same reason.
Does she remind you of your aunt as well?
Eve is probably more like my uncle.
Her gender and her manner
of speech are different,
but she has the same heart.
My aunt and uncle are the only the
reason I want to return to my world.
As for Lis...
she's like me.
Lis is?
We were in similar situations.
We were both abused in terrible environments.
The key difference is our hostility.
I'll eliminate anything that threatens me.
Touka Mimori isn't here to save the world.
Just to exact my own selfish revenge.
I'm not a good person.
If you ever want out of
this quest for vengeance,
you're welcome to leave anytime.
This is purely so I can get even, after all.
I have my own share of thoughts
regarding Alion's goddess,
so I have no intention of leaving.
Especially not after you've given me
the important role of vice captain.
Well then...
To repay you for going along
on this journey with me,
I'll hear any one request you have.
Assuming it's within my power, of course.
Huh?
Go ahead and give it some thought.
I understand.
You should get some rest.
Good night, Sir Tooka.
Yeah.
Sleep.
Thank you very much.
You have good form.
You'll probably surpass me in terms
of pure technique at some point.
Though, please remember our promise.
Yes. I promise not to tell
anyone about our training.
It would be difficult to get
permission from Vicius if you do.
You will become stronger, Ayaka Sogou.
Um, Nyantan-san,
why did you agree to help me?
You resemble my little sister.
It's eat or be eaten in this world.
Show any weakness, and you'll fall
prey to intrigue and violence in no time.
Remember that.
Some say it puts more
emphasis on appearance,
but it certainly does its job.
Are you sure about this, Lis?
Of course!
Thank you so much, Sir Tooka!
You don't have to force yourself.
That's not the case at all!
I'm happy that you bought this for me!
Sir Tooka.
Hmm?
Isn't it about time we came up with
a name for our mercenary band?
A name?
Yes. We might need to identify ourselves
on the other side of the Land of Monsters.
I have one idea to propose.
What do you think of
"The Lord of the Flies' Warband"?
It's what the army led by the
Lord of the Flies was called.
The Lord of the Flies' Warband?
I think it's a good name.
I-I think so too.
It's not bad.
All right, let's go with that.
So this is the Land of Monsters...
What's that?
A corrupted tree.
They say it used be a sacred tree.
Tooka, pour some magic into my right hand.
Magic?
Yes, please.
This crest was only passed down to our
tribe's leader and their children.
The green dot represents
our present location,
and the red dot represents
the Witch of Taboos, or so I was taught.
So we just need to go in the direction
that connects the two lights.
It's not fading at all.
I'm sure time will ease it.
I'm sure time will fix everything.
No, it won't.
My thirst for vengeance against
that damn goddess isn't receding at all.
So what if I'm a fool?
So what if it's disgraceful?
I may be the foolish and
disgraceful Touka Mimori,
but I will show the Goddess Vicius hell!
The Land of Golden-Eyed Monsters
throws us in great danger,
but at the same time,
it's packed with experience points.
I might never catch up to the
S-Class and A-Class heroes,
but I can close the gap between us.
Which gives me good reason to level up.
I'll kill and kill and kill.
I'll annihilate everything in the
Land of Monsters and turn them into EXP!
You've all leveled up a surprising amount.
KIRIHARA'S GROUP
- You have my gratitude for all the
hard work you've put in thus far.
YASU'S GROUP
- However, increasing your level only
means increasing your base stats.
SOGOU'S GROUP
- However, increasing your level only
means increasing your base stats.
SOGOU'S GROUP
- You all still lack skill in combat,
namely technique.
IKUSABA'S GROUP
- You all still lack skill in combat,
namely technique.
THE TAKAO SISTERS
- So, with that in mind, I've summoned famous
figures from every nation to train you.
So, with that in mind, I've summoned famous
THE FOUR SAINTS
- These people...
- They're all incredibly strong.
BANEWOLF
At this time, we've confirmed the Great Demon
Empire's forces are making a major move.
Our next battle against the Great
Demon Empire's army will likely
be a grand battle well
beyond our expectations.
So,
the heroes our Alion prides itself on,
meaning you all, will be participating.
We must have all the heroes
continue to level up
while they learn actual combat.
So soon enough,
I plan to have them head for the
Land of Golden-Eyed Monsters.
This technology is unbelievable.
What is this carved into the white portion?
It's super yummy!
I've never had anything
so delicious in my life!
I see.
It's good, isn't it, little Piggymaru?
I can scarcely believe it.
What's the matter, Seras?
I love it.
Oh, no, it's nothing.
These baked sweets are very delicious.
LAND OF THE GOLDEN-EYED MONSTERS